http://www.metawerx.net/privacy.htm

Explore
What can I run?
Secure IMAP Mail
Why Metawerx?
Contact Us
Sign Up!
Privacy and Security Statement
Metawerx Pty Ltd recognises that your privacy is very important to you. Providing your personal information is an act of trust that we take very seriously. Metawerx Pty Ltd will not sell, trade, give or rent any information obtained from you to any third parties.
We acknowledge that we will collect and store information about you as part of offering and providing services to you. In this regard, we will act ethically and as evidence of this commitment, we will take reasonable steps to comply with the following principles in relation to the information you provide to us about you.
Metawerx Pty Ltd may from time to time amend, update, or change this Statement. You should check this page periodically for changes to this Privacy Statement.
Collection
Metawerx Pty Ltd collects the personal data that you volunteer on registration for any of the services or products on our website, via email, or through other forms.
This information will only be collected by lawful and fair means.
In order to register with the Metawerx Website we require some basic information about you. We also allow you to provide additional non-required information on registration and at other times. Only information marked, as "required" during registration is needed to use our services. This information is used for identification purposes, billing purposes and to contact you when necessary.
As you browse the Metawerx Website we may log the IP address of your computer, session details, and domain name to evaluate which parts of the Website you visit and how long you stay there. This tracking does not link your computer's IP address with any other information you have submitted to us. While a Metawerx user's session may be tracked, all users remain anonymous when tracked.
IP tracking information is aggregated with tracking data from all site visitors to measure number of visits, average time spent on the Website, pages viewed, and to help diagnose problems with our server.
Use and disclosure
Metawerx Pty Ltd requires you to provide certain information about yourself in order to provide services to you. We will not rent, sell or exchange information about you to third parties (other than related parties) except where you consent, or except where you would expect the information to be disclosed, or except where we have indicated we may disclose, or except where we are legally obliged to disclose such information.
Data quality
Metawerx Pty Ltd will take reasonable steps to ensure that information we have about you is accurate, complete and up to date when we collect and use it.
Data security
Metawerx Pty Ltd will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we hold about you is kept secure at all times.
Metawerx Pty Ltd will limit access to your personal information to employees and data processors that need it to carry out the service provided by us except where we inform you otherwise. Our employees and data processors are obliged to respect the confidentiality of clients' and website visitors' personal data. Metawerx Pty Ltd will reinforce with other employees the policies and practices in relation to safeguarding personal information of clients and visitors, preventing its unauthorised access, use or disclosure, and ensuring its proper handling.
Our website has policies, rules and measures in place to protect the visitor's personal data from:
Unauthorised access;
Improper use;
Alteration;
Unlawful or accidental destruction; and
Accidental loss.
Openness
Metawerx Pty Ltd will be honest and open with you about the type of personal information that is collected about you and the actual use of any such information. By giving out your personal information, or completing forms on our Website, you have consented to the use of this information for contact purposes regarding your account or enquiry.
If you have agreed to receive marketing information, then you have consented to the use of this information in future for marketing campaigns run by Metawerx Pty Ltd.
At any time you have the option to opt-out from receiving any future communications from Metawerx Pty Ltd by contacting us.
Access and correction
If you provide us with satisfactory personal identification, such as your login details, Metawerx Pty Ltd will let you have access to the information we keep about you and give you the opportunity to have that information corrected if it is found to be incorrect.
Further, if Metawerx Pty Ltd is not able to release details of personal information to you, then we will provide you with reasons for any denial of access or correction.
Anonymity
You can access our web site home page and browse the public area of the Metawerx Pty Ltd Website without disclosing personal information.
Metawerx Pty Ltd will, wherever it is lawful and practicable, give you the option of not identifying yourself to us except where it is necessary to use our Website services.
Transfer of Data
Metawerx Pty Ltd will take reasonable steps to ensure that if any information you give us about you will remain subject to the protection given by our Privacy Statement or another statute or binding scheme which is substantially similar to this Privacy Statement.
Sensitive Information
Metawerx Pty Ltd will not collect information that is considered highly personal or highly sensitive about you. For example, information relating to your racial or ethnic origin, religious or philosophical beliefs, sexual orientation or in relation to your health will not be collected by us.
Protecting Your Credit Card Information
The credit card information provided by you to Metawerx Pty Ltd will be encrypted using a minimum of AES-256 encryption and stored in a confidential manner.
Where you have authorised us to automatically debit your card on our payments page we will retain your card information until the credit card expires, or your account is closed, or you instruct us to erase the information.
Where you have not authorised us to automatically debit your card, card information is retained until processing of your payment is complete, and then erased from our internal systems.
Our employees may access such information from our payment processor (National Australia Bank) only when there is an appropriate business reason to do so, such as when a refund must be issued back to the credit card.
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your information, and our employees are required to follow these privacy standards.
Transaction Security
The Metawerx website uses the Transport Layer Security (SSL/TLS) protocol to ensure transaction security between your browser and our server, and between our server and our payment processor (National Australia Bank).
Ciphers used are PCI-compliant (as verified by Qualys SSLLabs at Feb 2013).
Data Ownership
Where data is uploaded to your Metawerx File System, Subversion or Database, except as required by law, we agree that you retain ownership and intellectual property rights over such data.
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your data, and our employees are required to follow these policies.
Cookies
Metawerx Pty Ltd uses cookies to hold session information, improve security during a visitor's session online, ensure effective advertising tailored to the visitor's needs, and provide you with your information.
We store the following information in cookies: your unique user ID
You can use your browser to disable cookies; Metawerx Pty Ltd is not liable for any errors which may be encountered with the Website as a result.
Our site uses Social Networking plugins from Twitter, Google and Facebook.
Please refer to the Privacy Policies of these services for more information on their use of cookies.
Some pages on our site use the MyWot trust or reputation badge.
Please refer to the WOT Privacy Policy for more information on their use of cookies.
Some pages on our site use StartSSL trust or reputation badge.
Please refer to the StartSSL Privacy Policy for more information on their use of cookies.
Client and Visitor Choice
By registering with Metawerx Pty Ltd you agree to receive information from our website.
We will send Metawerx News updates which may include marketing information about our services.
At any time you can Opt Out from receiving any further information using any of the following methods:
Postal Address:
Metawerx Pty Ltd
Level 8, 350 Collins Street
Melbourne, VIC, 3000
Australia
Telephone: 1300 88 40 60
Email: (see our Contact Us pages - our email address is not listed here due to possible abuse)
Coverage and Complaints
Our Privacy Statement covers Metawerx Pty Ltd ACN 108 719 955 and the Metawerx Pty Ltd Website:
If you would like to make a complaint on the basis that you feel your privacy has been breached because we have failed to comply with this Privacy Statement, you should contact us using the following methods:
Postal Address:
Email: (see our Contact Details pages - our email address is not listed here due to possible SPAM)
Why Host With Us?
